{
    "id": "8242fd7ae814459ca5058afd4d8e9fe7",
    "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I ……………………… about your problems, I would have helped you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9bce445d8e75418f8749720449720dc2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has agreed to ……………………….. my dogs while I am away on holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look at",
                "look for",
                "look after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f63028d3f3a4c2a8effc83204c30ff2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They made the child ………………………. the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "to drink",
                "drinking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a66118f592a42c48b4098a88811ca97"
        },
        {
            "question": "She makes her children ……………………………… their lessons everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "learn",
                "to learn",
                "learning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c94c0dc229a4112a146ff071b72c835"
        },
        {
            "question": "The test was …………………… .. difficult that she couldn’t answer many questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da1edeeade054c73bd21a4b644023f77"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. this work by next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would finish",
                "will finish",
                "will have finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58911bf88fc3472ea9b82f3ba4412dfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… by the time we arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0b19ab12a774d6aa5e0727f8ca77772"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I stopped …………………….. to him, he was working in his garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaking",
                "to speak",
                "speak"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8dc6ed24ca94d95b1aa0ac679669e91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Despite ……………………. hard, he failed the exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "to work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fc1702c800c45579953cb3d85546b77"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. play a lot of tennis when he was young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "was to",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4749c858aca453eb07a77154359f1cb"
        }
    ]
}